[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Uh...
I'm sorry, I'm...
a bit tipsy.
I think I'll see you
tomorrow in the hotel.
Are you sure you're okay?
Okay.
Uh...
Bye.
Thank you.
[DOOR OPENS]
Take care.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
Because I care.
[DOOR CLOSES]
- [SQUEALS]
- [PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh my god. Yes!
Yes! Yes!
[SQUEALS]
[GIGGLING]
Yes! Yes!
[SMOOCHES, GIGGLES]
- [EXHALES SOFTLY, SQUEALS]
- [KNOCKING ON DOOR]
[KNOCKING CONTINUES]
Gosh. He misses me already?
Isn't it too soon? [GIGGLES]
- [KNOCKING CONTINUES]
- [DOOR OPENS]
[GRIM MUSIC PLAYING]
M-Madam...
[GRIM MUSIC CONTINUES]
I won't take long.
I know you only want this.
[GRIM MUSIC CONTINUES]
Stop pestering my husband!
I don't want to see you again.
[HUFFS]
[GRIM MUSIC CONTINUES]